Otsego County Conservation Association; Records apap158
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Otsego County Conservation Association Records
1967-2001
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Otsego County Conservation Association
apap158
6.4 cubic ft.
Records of association dedicated to the protection, appreciation, and enhancement of natural resources in and around Otsego County. The group is concerned about numerous issues including the preservation of the Otsego Lake watershed, solid waste management, land-use planning, and water quality.
Administrative History
The Otsego County Conservation Association (usually abbreviated OCCA) was founded in 1968 as a nonprofit organization dedicated to the protection of natural resources within Otsego County ["History", http://www.occainfo.org/pages/history.html, 13 August 2004]. Founder Frederick H. V. Mecklenberg, known as "Mecky" to friends, remained an active force and an inspirational figure in OCCA from its earliest days until his death in 1991.
The primary goals of OCCA are to support and promote the conservation of Otsego County's natural resources; to support and publicize conservation-related educational programs; to cooperate with similar organizations and with all levels of government to "promote maximum benefit from privately owned rural land"; and to enhance appreciation for rural living ["Bylaws of the Otsego County Conservation Association, Incorporated", 13 September 1990, Series 1, Box 1, Folder 18].
OCCA is governed by an elected board of volunteer directors. Officers include a president, a vice-president, a secretary, and a treasurer. The Board of Directors meets monthly. Full membership meetings are held annually, usually in October. Committees, which form to address specific issues, include the Otsego Lake Committee, the Land Use Committee, the Conservation Education Committee, and the Scientific Advisory Committee ["Mission Statement", May 1991, Series 1, Box 3, Folder 3].
In 1994, OCCA hired its first full-time employee. Teresa Winchester was originally hired as Coordinator, but her title was later changed to Executive Director.
OCCA has long enjoyed a close relationship with the State University of New York College at Oneonta's Biological Field Station, a research facility located along the shore of Otsego Lake. The Field Station's longtime director, Willard Harman, has served as OCCA president, and from 1991-1993 OCCA provided funding for an Environmental Administrator at the Field Station, J. Joseph Homberger. OCCA has also collaborated with other local and regional environmental organizations on issues of mutual concern; most notably with Otsego 2000 on issues such as the Glimmerglass State Park proposed motor boat launch in the 1990s.
Presidents of OCCA in the years covered by this collection were:
Frederick H. V. Mecklenberg, 1968-1973
John Olsen, 1973-1975
Willard Harman, 1975-1978
Bill Powers, 1978-1979
Willard Harman, 1979-1981
Irene Mozolewski, 1981-1989
Lewis Hamilton, 1989-1992
James Austin, 1992-1994
Bonnie Canning Hoffman, 1994-1997
Edna Holowachuk, 1997-2000
James Bernegger, 2000-
Scope and Contents
This collection covers OCCA's administration from its founding in 1968 through 2001. Activities of the Board of Directors are well-documented through meeting agendas, minutes, and correspondence. There are detailed reports on the activities of the OCCA Coordinator and the Biological Field Station's Environmental Administrator. Monthly treasurer's reports provide evidence of OCCA's financial affairs. Evidence of committee activity is limited. However, there are files for the Scientific Advisory Committee, the Otsego Lake Committee, the Financial Committee, and the Executive Committee.
The collection also contains a great deal of information on OCCA's environmental initiatives within Otsego County, particularly during the 1990s. Best-documented are OCCA's activities related to Otsego Lake and to solid waste management. The Otsego Lake files include a great deal of material on OCCA's opposition to a motor boat launch in Glimmerglass State Park, proposed by the New York State Department of Environmental Conservation. Other Otsego Lake issues covered by this collection include commercial and residential development along the shore of the lake, fish and fishery management, lake management, and watershed management. The solid waste files focus on controversy related to the Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority (MOSA), a three-county solid waste consortium that proved extremely costly to Otsego County in the mid to late 1990s.
There are also files related to other environmental projects and issues. These include files on the Cherry Valley Sewer Initiative, the Wal-Mart distribution center in Sharon Springs, and Otsego 2000s lawsuit against the County Planning Board, as well as subject files on general issues of environmental concern such as agriculture and water pollution.
Other OCCA activities are not as well-documented. OCCA offers annual fellowships and assistantships to researchers at the SUNY Oneonta Biological Field Station, and sponsors several students each year at the Department of Environmental Conservation's summer camp for children and teens. However, information on these activities is limited. There is also not much information on membership involvement in the organization, apart from minutes and agendas from the annual membership meeting.
Arrangement of the Collection
Divided into 4 topical file series.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, by Teresa Winchester, Executive Director of Otsego County Conservation Association, in April 2003 and March 2004.
Related Materials
For related collections in the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives, see the online Conservation and the Environment subject guide at http://library.albany.edu/speccoll/conservation.htm.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Environmental health -- Political aspects -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Social ecology -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Environmental policy -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Environmental health -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Environmental management -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Environmental protection -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Refuse and refuse disposal -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Water -- Pollution -- New York (State) -- Otsego County.; Minutes.; Correspondence.; Agendas.; Budgets.; Bylaws.; Clippings.; Newsletters.; Reports.; Agriculture; Conservation and the Environment; Neighborhood and Community Associations; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Mecklenberg, Frederick H.V.; Olsen, John.; Harman, Willard N.; Powers, Bill.; Mozolewski, Irene.; Hamilton, Lewis.; Austin, James.; Canning Hoffman, Bonnie.; Holowachuk, Edna.; Bernegger, James.; Homberger, J. Joseph.; Holowachuk, Edna.; Winchester, Teresa.; Otsego 2000.; Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority.; New York (State). Department of Environmental Conservation.
- Administrative Files, 1967-2001; 1; 2.5 cubic ft.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains material related to the administration of the Association, dating from its incorporation in 1968 through 2001. Included are a near-complete run of board meeting agendas and minutes, monthly financial reports, by-laws, incoming and outgoing correspondence of board presidents and the executive director, committee reports, monthly reports from the Coordinator, and copies of OCCA's official newsletter. There are also some membership lists, a book tracking members and their dues payments from 1972-1988, and minutes from annual membership meetings. Because of the close relationship between SUNY Oneonta's Biological Field Station and OCCA, files related to the Field Station, such as the files of the Environmental Administrator, are included in this series. The Environmental Administrator's files consist primarily of reading files, which contain extensive outgoing correspondence, memos and reports written by the Environmental Administrator from 1991-1993.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Biological Field Station, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Biological Field Station, Reading File, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Board of Directors, 1969-1970; 1972; 1974-1982; 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1972; 1975-1976; 1982-1984 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, Correspondence and Miscellaneous, 1992-1995; 2000; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1968-1977 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1978-1983 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1997-1999 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Board of Directors, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1988-2000 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - By-laws, 1970; 1981-1984; 1990; 1998; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Contributions, Correspondence, 1986-1988; 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Coordinator's Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1971-1985; 1988-1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1999-2001; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Incoming, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Environmental Administrator, Position Description and Goals, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Environmental Administrator, Reading File, 1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Environmental Administrator, Reading File, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8-10)
  - Environmental Administrator, Reading File, 1993 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11-12)
  - Environmental Administrator, Reports and Memos, 1991-1993 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - Executive Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1970; 1972; 1976; 1982-1987; 2001 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - Financial Committee, 1988; 1990-1991; 1993; 1995 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Financial Ledger, 1973-1979 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Financial Report, Draft, 1986; 1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Incorporation Certificate, 1968; 1972 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Incorporation Meeting, Minutes, 1968 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Key Trust Company, OCCA Asset Report, 1992 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Land Use Planning Committee, Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - Meeting Notes, 1990; 1994-1995; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - Membership Dues Payment Record Book, A-D, 1972-1988 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Membership Dues Payment Record Book, E-K, 1972-1988 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Membership Dues Payment Record Book, L-Q, 1972-1988 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Membership Dues Payment Record Book, R-Z, Honorary Members, 1972-1988 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Membership Lists and Membership Reports, 1980; 1982-1984; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Membership Meetings, Annual, 1967-1986; 1988-1989; 1993-1997; 2000 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Membership Survey, Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Mission Statement, 1990-1991; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Newsletters, 1973-1988; 1990-1991 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Newsletters, 1992-1994; 1999; 2001 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Norstar Trust Company, Investment Performance Review, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Otsego Lake Committee, 1973; 1976-1978; 1980-1983; 1992-1993 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Policy, 1988; 1993; 1999 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Sale of Assets, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1985; 1987-1989 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Scientific Advisory Committee, 1990-1995 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Treasurer's and Controller's Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1979-1980; 1983-1986 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1990-1995 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1996-2000 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
- Otsego Lake, 1973-1997; 1999; 2; 1.4 cubic ft.
  This series documents the Association's work related to Otsego Lake. Central to this series are files documenting the Association's opposition to a proposed motor boat launch in Glimmerglass State Park. These files include correspondence, news clippings, reports, and responses to a major public opinion survey conducted by the Association in 1995. This series also contains material on other lake-related issues, such as boating and public access, development, fish and fishery management, lake management plans, and watershed management plans.
  - Boating, Environmental Impact, 1974-1975; 1979; 1982; 1985-1988; 1990-1992 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 1)
  - Comparison of the Otsego Lake Macrobenthos Communities between 1935 and 1993, ca. 1994 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 2)
  - Development, 1983-1986; Undated (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 3)
  - Development, Five Mile Point, 1985; 1987-1989 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 4)
  - Draft Strategic Public Use and Access Plan for Fishing and Boating, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 5)
  - Fish, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 6)
  - Fisheries Management, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 7)
  - "The Future of Otsego Lake Country Is in Your Hands", Brochure, Undated (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 8)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, 1988-1992 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 9)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 10)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 11)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 12)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Undated (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 13)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Correspondence, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 14)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 15)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Correspondence, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 16)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Glimmerglass Coalition, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 17)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Motorized Vehicles, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 18)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, News Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 19)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Publicity Materials, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 20)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, State Environmental Quality Review Assessment Form, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 21)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Surveys, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 22-24)
  - Glimmerglass State Park Proposed Boat Launch, Willard Harman Memorandum, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 25)
  - Lake Cleanup Day, 1973; 1993 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 26)
  - Lake Commission, 1994 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 27)
  - Lake Management, Alternatives, Undated (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 28)
  - Lake Management, Background Documentation, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 29)
  - Lake Management, Correspondence, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 30)
  - Lake Management, Other Lake Management Plans, 1987; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 31)
  - Legislation, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 32)
  - Motor Boats, 1982; 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 33)
  - Navigation Regulations, 1983; 1989; 1991-1994; Undated (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 34)
  - No-Wake Zone Regulations, Letters of Support, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 35)
  - Otsego 2000 and Otsego County Conservation Association, Joint Work, 1988; 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 36)
  - Otsego Facts, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 37)
  - Otsego Lake Watershed Geographic Information System, 1989; 1991 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 38)
  - "The Public Utilization and Perception of the Recreational Use of Otsego Lake", 1991 (Box 1 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 39)
  - Save Our Lake Otsego, 1984; Undated (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 1)
  - Septic Initiative, 1999; Undated (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 2)
  - State of the Lake Report, Undated (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 3)
  - Use Regulations, 1973; 1983-1984; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 4)
  - Village of Cooperstown, Watershed Supervisory Committee, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 5)
  - Water Level Data, 1974-1987 (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 6)
  - Water Quality, 1987; 1992-1993; 1997; Undated (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 7)
  - Watershed, Land Use Proposal, 1987 (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 8)
  - Watershed Management, Background Documentation, 1985; 1996-1997 (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 9)
  - Watershed Management Plan, 1997 (Box 2 (2-Otsego Lake), Folder 10)
- Solid Waste Management, 1987-1991; 3; 1 cubic foot
  This series documents OCCA's concern with and activities related to solid waste management in Otsego County. Many files document MOSA, the Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority. MOSA files consist mostly of correspondence, news clippings, and reports. They provide detailed documentation of public dissatisfaction with MOSA and Otsego County's legal struggles with the Authority. There are also numerous subject files on solid waste management in other New York State counties, as well as files on general waste management issues.
  - Brookman Disposal Transfer Station, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 1)
  - Broome County Solid Waste Management, 1994-1996; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 2)
  - Chenango County Solid Waste Management, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 3)
  - Cornell Waste Management Institute, 1994-1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 4)
  - County and Local Laws, 1989-1990; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 5)
  - Court Rulings, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 6)
  - Delaware County Solid Waste Management, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 7)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, Bureau of Waste Reduction and Recycling, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 8)
  - Department of Environmental Conservation, Cleanup Policy and Guidelines, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 9)
  - Grants and Funding, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 10)
  - Enviro-Tech Resources, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 11)
  - Flow Control, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 12)
  - Green Waste Composting, Village of Cooperstown, 1992; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 13)
  - Haulers, Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 14)
  - Incinerator, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 15)
  - Interviews, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 16)
  - Landfill Siting, 1993; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 17)
  - Landfills, Technical, 1986; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 18)
  - Legislation and Court Cases, 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 19)
  - Madison County Department of Solid Waste and Sanitation, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 20)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 21)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Annual Report, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 22)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Board Meetings, 1995-1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 23)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Consultant's Report, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 24)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, County Board Resolutions, 1987-1989; 1995 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 25)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Guaranteed Annual Tonnage, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 26)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, League of Women Voters, 1987-1989; 1995 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 27)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Legislation, 1987-1988; 1994 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 28)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Meetings, Hearings, and Interviews, 1995-1996; 2000 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 29)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, News Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 30)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 31)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, News Clippings, 1997 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 32)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, News Clippings, 1998-2000; Undated (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 33)
  - Montgomery-Otsego-Schoharie Solid Waste Management Authority, Request for Proposals, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (3-Solid Waste Management), Folder 34)